Don’t you give me your love and passion?
为什么不给我你的爱和激情
Believe in love, even though
相信着爱 即使
There’re borders and disturbance and more
存在隔阂干扰等等障碍
I’m the only one who loves you
我是唯一真正爱你的人
Because I’m crazy about you
因为我为你疯狂
Let’s ride to hell.　追従してGo
直驶至地狱吧 我会一路追随你
一緒なら寧ろ死にたいじゃない
若是与你同在 即刻就死又有何妨
Beyond the line　果てなんかない
在边界之外 并不存在尽头
I swear, I’m gonna be so fucking grateful
我发誓 我会将无上感恩
Blessing word　貴方は至高
祝福的话语 您是至高无上的
命令に　Your highness　忠実にFollow
对于您的命令 我必将忠实服从
You give orders　渡しはしない
您下达的指示 我必将亲力亲为
何より尊い存在よ
高于一切的存在啊
You don’t know why my love is crying
你并不知道为什么我的爱在流泪
凝着したい　過剰なくらい
我想粘着你 腻到你厌烦
永遠になりたい　Don’t wanna cry
想永远在一起 不想要哭泣
嫉妬妄想狂いそうよ
几乎要被嫉妒和妄想逼疯了
Don’t you give me your love and passion?
为什么不给我你的爱和激情
愛とは暴動衝動　Let go
所谓爱就是暴动的冲动 释放吧
精神以上に本能、心臓まで　More　要求したい
我想要你的灵魂 你的本能和心脏 想要你的一切
I don’t want to live in a world without you
我无法活在没有你的世界
貴方以外のこの未来を　Kill it, kill it
若是未来没有你 抹杀 抹杀
I would be happy to kill it for my love
为了我的爱 我乐意牺牲未来
I’m imaging now. if you’re mine,
我能想像 若是拥有了你
It’s like a paradise and haven and more
这里便是天堂 我便拥有了所有
You’re the only man who I love
你是我的真命天子 我只爱你一个
In my life and destiny and all
这便是我的宿命缘分 我的一切
Don’t you give me your love and passion?
为什么不给我你的爱和激情
I know the border. It should be wrecked, go
我知道有障碍 我要打破它 出发